programmingbulls.com 2011-05-15

# Privacy Policy

This _Comment_ will be submitted for moderation and will not be accessible to other users until it has been approved.

Programmingbulls respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## Information Collection and Use

Programmingbulls collects personal information when you register with Programmingbulls . This is optional and for registration purposes only. Registration allows you to participate in the Programmingbulls activities and allows us to identify you as a unique member of the Programmingbulls.

We do not collect personal information when you visit our site unless you signup for a service, place an order, register, complete a survey or enter a contest. When you signup for a service, we will ask you for the following personal information: name and e-mail address. We may use your personal information to contact you for account purposes. When you place an order, we will ask you for the following personal information: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and its expiration date. This information is requested to verify your identity. This information is transmitted via a secure encrypted server using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, the approved industry standard. We may use your personal information to contact you for account purposes. When you submit feedback or questions via e-mail, or contact us for information about our Web site, we will request your name and e-mail address. We use this information solely to respond to your inquiries.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Programmingbulls certifies that all personal information relating to its members and clients, including email addresses and personal information, will be kept confidential. We do not share, sell, rent or barter any identifiable personal information to any third party.

## Advertisments & Resources

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative, or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

You can find additional information in Appendix A of the NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers (PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time.

## Cookies

From time to time, Programmingbulls or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of Programmingbulls 's you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers and we may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

By using the Programmingbulls, you consent to the collection and use of information by Programmingbulls as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

## Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or comments about Programmingbulls's privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at:  
Programmingbulls@gmail.com.

## People interested in above are also interested in: 

  * ### PHP Cookies

What are Cookies?

Cookie is a piece of information that is stored as text files on the visitor's browser/computer. This allows the website server to keep track of what a visitor is doing during their visit (or even across multiple visits).

As an example to this is Amazon.com: do you notice that if you visit Amazon.com, Amazon keeps track of the click you have made. Even if you come to the site after sometime, it knows that you had visited earlier and would show you your earlier visits. This happens because Amazon.com stores cookies on your computer.

  * ### Tomcat: Cookies lenght problem

Hi,

I'm creating and attaching a cooking for my application with some useful information. 

But this information is not accessible after that.

The problem is that when I try to attach too much information, my cookie is not passed forward. When I try to attach few information it's OK.

My questions:

What is the max length for cookies values?  
If it's a bug, there is any workaround for Tomcat 5.5?

I'm creating my cookie using the following code:

  * ### Bowser bugs – helping e-Commerce sites/Ad firms

The practice of online hacking of confidential and personal data is not new to the cyber world. Events which may not look as acute as hacking are equally profitable for those who’ve been driving the illegitimate exercise on the internet over the years.

  * ### PHP Regex for file/path

Hi,

What would be the php regex to match any one of the following:

privacy.html  
privacy.htm  
privacy  
w3c/privacy.html  
w3c/privacy.htm  
w3c/privacy

thanks

JP

Hi,

What would be the php regex to match any one of the following:

privacy.html  
privacy.htm  
privacy  
w3c/privacy.html  
w3c/privacy.htm  
w3c/privacy

thanks

JP

Original Question by: JP19

  * ### Is it possible to check if user has cookies enabled in php without a page reload?

For example, code such as the following doesn't seem to work, even if the cookie is actually set, until I refresh the page.

  * ### Cross-login and parsing user specific data

Hey,

I want to develop an application for a website which provides user specific information. These user specific information of course are just visible as long as you're logged-in. Json-interface and parser will be hosted on a different server and I'm wondering how to handle the login + maintain a session in order to parse the data. The loginscript of the website which I want to parse is using POST and puts a cookie with username + md5 password. 

These are all information I can provide. Thanks in advance.

  * ### Contact Us form and email not working

forgive me if this subject is here, but i can't seem to track it down. i'm brand new to drupal- spent the last few years developing in joomla.  
i've just put up my first site, and it appears that the site sends mail to ANY email address (i.e.: @earthlink.net, @mac.com, @me.com, etc) except to an address @ my site name. 

  * ### How to find number of CPU processors on a Linux machine

You can find the number or processors on your linux machine as follows:

shell> grep processor /proc/cpuinfo

This would give output like (which means the following computer has 8 processors:

processor : 0  
processor : 1  
processor : 2  
processor : 3  
processor : 4  
processor : 5  
processor : 6  
processor : 7
